

Tufan Recep SARI

Frontend Developer



+90 534 830 56 67



www.linkedin.com/in/tufan-sari



tufanrsari@gmail.com



https://github.com/tufansari

SUMMARY

I have experience at web front-end technologies. Focused on web front-end, so improving javascript's libraries, frameworks and trying to carry higher level. I also have experience in education. That's why I believe I'm good at relationships and communication with people. I will adapt to your vision and try to move forward. In addition to, optimistic and personable individual enthusiastic about meeting new people. Strong presentation skills and a real researcher.

CAREER

- 12.06.2023
- 01.04.2023

Freelance

- FRONTEND DEVELOPER
- Construction of an e-commerce site similar in functionality to Google Maps with Chakra UI.
- Web services APIs, RESTful API.
- 01.04.2023
- 20.01.2023

Abb Garjan Group

- FRONTEND DEVELOPER
- UI design with specific frameworks like Material
 UI and DevExpress.
- Creating reusable components and making them ready to use web services APIs and UX.
- 11.10.2022
- 11.05.2022

Smartpro Academy

- **WEB DEVELOPER**
- Full stack development.
- Intern.

• 2020-2021

HUMAN RELATIONS OFFICER

Enthoosia

Provide operation management and flow.

• 2017-2018

TEACHER

Capa Science High School

- Administered assessments to determine each student's specific edicational and social needs.
 Kept students on-task with proactive behavior modification and positive reinforcement strategies.
- Prepared quizzes, tests and examinations to gauge how well students were learning.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- RESTful API
- SASS & SCSS

ASP.NET MVC

AzureDevOps

- TypeScript
- UI Design
- HTML
- Postman

- React.js
- Material UI

Bootstrap

- CSS
- Firebase

- Node.jsJQuery
- Tailwind
- C#
- ChakraUI

Git

ONLINE COURSES

HTTP Networking Course – Fetch and REST APIs in JavaScript/ freeCodeCamp.org

React, Redux and Hooks bootcamp/ Engin Demirog

Web programming with React / Turkcell-Gelecegi Yazanlar.

C# Programming camp / Engin Demirog

EDUCATION

• 2019

PEDAGOGY

Marmara University • Master's Degree.

• 2014-2018

BIOLOGY TEACHER EDUCATION

Marmara University • Bachelor's Degree.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

- TALK
- Upper intermediate.
- WRITING
- Advanced.

TURKISH

• Native Language.

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate,

Exam: Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure,

React 101.

REFERENCES

Orhan Umit Keskin - Product Owner at AnnounceKit

+90 (530) 667 06 19

Cihan Kilinckaya - Manager at Apple

+90 (532) 280 47 35

Tugay Aydin - Software Instructor

+90 (542) 332 14 52